>> Kyle Simpson: 在接下来的第 5 行，因为肯定有问题
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Moving on then to line
five because there's certainly a question
关于第 5 行的事情
as to what's gonna happen with line five.
这个主题变量会发生什么 ?
What's gonna happen with
this topic variable?
同样的问题也会有同样的过程
Well, it's gonna process exactly the same,
same questions.
这就是为什么我要教你他们的叙事
That's why I'm teaching
you their narrative.
那么这个开始是怎样的呢 ?
So how does that start?
你的范围
Hey scope of.
>> 扬声器 2: 其他类。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Other class.
>> Kyle Simpson: 其他类。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Other class.
我有什么参考?
I have a what kind of reference?
>> 演讲者 3: 目标。 >> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我有一个目标
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Target.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have a target
请参考，谢谢。
reference, thank you.
我有一个标识主题的目标引用。
I have a target reference for
the identifier topic.
听说过吗
Ever heard of it?
>> 扬声器 2: 否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: No.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 接下来我们要去哪里 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So where do we go next?
>> 扬声器 2: 全局作用域。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Global scope.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 全球范围。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A global scope.
我有一个叫做话题的变量的目标参考。
I have a target reference for
the variable called topic.
听说过吗
Ever heard of it?
答案是吗 ?
And the answer is?
>> 演讲者 3: 否。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: No.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们希望答案是 " 否" 。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Well we would like for
the answer to be no.
答案是否正确，似乎是很合理的。
It seems very reasonable for
the answer to be no.
事实上似乎有点疯狂的是除了你之外
In fact it seems somewhat crazy that it
would ever be anything other than no but
我们在这里看到的是一个历史上的坏的部分
here we see one of the historical
bad parts of JavaScript which is in
对那些没有被允许的人尽可能的宽容
the early days to be as forgiving
as possible for people that didn't
了解语言，他们提出了这个全球汽车的概念。
understand the language, they
instituted this idea of auto global's.
因此，如果您尝试分配一个从未正式声明的变量。
So if you try to assign to a variable
that's never been formally declared.
一旦到达全球范围，如果你说全球范围，
Once you arrive at the global scope,
if you say hey, global scope,
我在找这个叫做 " 话题 " 的话题
I'm looking for this marble called topic,
ever heard of it?
而全球范围并不是说不，对不起的错误，
And the global scope instead
of saying nope, sorry error,
全球范围会说我为你创造了一个
the global scope's gonna say
I just created one for you.
我没帮你
Aren't I helpful.
它会给我们一个红色的大理石，而不是蓝色的大理石。
And it's gonna hand us a red marble,
not a blue marble.
你为什么要用红色的大理石而不是蓝色的大理石
Why do you suppose it only hands us
a red marble and not a blue marble?
>> 演讲者 4: 因为它是非全局的。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Because it is non globally.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们现在正在讨论全球范围。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Cuz we're
talking to the global scope now.
我们已经把已经正式宣布的范围
We've already passed up the scope where
that would have been formally declared and
现在我们在讨论全球范围
now we're talking to the global scope and
它是全球范围让我们变的
it's the global scope that
gives us the variable.
你和我一起吗
Are you with me?
所以我们创建了一个全球性的
So we've created an auto
global called topic which
听起来很可怕因为太可怕了
that sounds terrible
because it is terrible.
但现在有一个全球性的变量叫做话题
But now there's a global
variable called topic and
当我们把红色大理石放在第 5 行的时候
when we get that red marble back and
make the assignment on line five,
现在有一个全球性的变量值重新处理好吗
there's a global variable now
with the value React in it, okay?
>> 演讲者 4: 所以话题就像老师说没有差别
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So topic is just like
teacher saying there's no difference then
在全球范围内
at the global level there too.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我不会说没有区别。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I wouldn't
say there's no difference.
当然，在编译时创建声明并
Certainly creating a declaration
at compile time and
在运行时期间动态创建，具有差异。
creating it dynamically during
the run time, have differences.
有性能差异和其他类型的事情
There are performance differences and
other sorts of things but
在这一点上机械地是两个全局变量
mechanically they are two global
variables at this point okay.
>> 演讲者 4: 如果你把它包起来，它就会产生差异
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Or down the road if you wrap
it around then it will make difference
因为它会再次出现
because it would pop again up.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，我的意思是，如果这不是全球范围的话。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, I mean if this
wasn't the global scope again then.
>> 扬声器 4: 但如果稍后再次出现。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: But
if erupted again later on and.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 老师不再是红色的大理石了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Teacher
wouldn't be a red marble anymore.
[ 相声]。
[CROSSTALK].
好吧不管你怎么解决这个问题
Okay, regardless of how you wrap your
brains around this just take this
特别的外卖，从来没有在任何情况下故意自动
particular takeaway, never ever under any
circumstances did you intentionally auto
创造了这样的世界
create global's like that.
始终声明要在其中使用声明的变量
Always declare the variables that
you want to use declare them in
无论您需要什么范围，但不要像这样自动创建它们，是。
whatever scope you need them in, but
don't auto create them like this, yes.
>> 扬声器 2: 如果主题相等，那么也会发生这种情况
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That would occur
also if topic equals react were
在老师变量的全球范围内。
in the global scope under
variable of teacher.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 这是真的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That's true.
嗯，对那个时候没有申报的变量的任何赋值，
Yeah, any assignment to a variable
that is undeclared at that moment,
任何我们都无法进入的范围
it is not available to any
scope that we have access to,
未声明到任何我们有权访问的范围。
not declared to any
scope we have access to.
任何未声明的变量都将最终创建此自动全局。
Any undeclared variable is going to
end up creating this auto global.
现在发生这种事的原因
Now, the reason why that happens
因为您会注意到此程序未在严格方式下运行。
is because you'll notice that this
program is not running in strict mode.
等一会儿我们再看紧模式的时候
And in just a moment,
we'll see when we flip on strict mode,
它会改变这种行为
it will change that behavior.
但这在非严格模式下运行，有时也称为懒人模式。
But this is running in the non-strict
mode or sometimes called, sloppy mode.
您应该使用严格方式，如果您使用的是严格方式，
You should be using strict mode,
and if you were using strict mode,
你就看不到这种行为了
you wouldn't see this behavior.
但既然这条密码闻不到就会这样
But since this code snip it isn't,
that's what happens,
当我们最终创建一个全球性的变量题目好吗 ?
as we end up creating a global
variable called topic, okay?
因此，执行将在该函数中执行。
So execution is then done in the function.
我们执行 console.log 的方式与我们之前的相同。
We execute console.log the same
way as we have before.
执行移至第 11 行。
Execution moves to line 11.
第 11 行的执行情况如何 ?
How does the execution of line 11 work?
我们要和一个范围，权利，和以前一样的对话，同样的叙事。
Hey, we gotta talk to a scope, right, same
conversation as before, same narrative.
嘿，全球范围，嘿红桶。
So hey, global scope, hey red bucket.
我有什么参考?
I have a what kind of reference?
>> 扬声器 3: 源引用。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Source reference.
>> Kyle Simpson: 对调用的变量的源引用 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: A source
reference to a variable called?
老师。 老师。
Teacher.
听说过吗 答案是吗 ?
Ever heard of it?
And the answer is?
>> 扬声器 3: 是。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yes.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我们去拿那个大理石，看看它的价值。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we go get that
marble and we look for its value.
它有什么价值 ?
And what value does it have?
>> 扬声器 3: 苏西。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Suzy.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 有苏西。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It has Suzy.
记得吗 因为第四行
Remember?
Because of line four,
我们分配给了一个红色的大理石
we assigned to a red marble.
我们已覆盖该变量中的值。
We've overwritten
the value in that variable.
这不是一个单独的变量，不是单独的大理石。
It's not a separate variable,
not a separate marble.
好了第 12 行第 12 行如何执行
Okay, line 12 then,
how does line 12 execute?
>> 演讲者 3: 全球范围。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Hey global scope.
>> Kyle Simpson: 全球范围，我有吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Hey global scope,
I have a?
>> 扬声器 3: 源。 >> Kyle Simpson: 源引用 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Source.
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Source reference for?
主题。 主题，你是专家，非常好。
Topic.
Topic, you're experts at this, very good.
你听过这个话题吗
Ever heard of topic?
全球范围会说吗
And global scope's gonna say?
这是你的红色大理石
Here's your red marble.
当我们看到红色大理石的价值时它会说吗 ?
And when we look at the value in
the red marble it's gonna say?
>> 扬声器 2: 重新操作。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: React.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 反应，反应。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: React, react.
>> 扬声器 3: 因此，如果第 11 行在第 9 行之前运行，那么老师仍将是顶部。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So if line 11 ran before
line 9, teacher would still be top.
>> Kyle Simpson: 再次道歉 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Say that again I'm sorry?
>> 演讲者 3: 因此，如果第 11 行实际上在第 8 行中。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: So
if line 11 was actually in line 8.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 我想你说的是第 12 行吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think
you're talking about line 12?
>演讲者 3: 我说的是第 11 行。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I'm talking about line 11.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, so
如果第 11 行在第 8 行，老师就会说凯尔，对。
if line 11 was on line 8 then
teacher would say Kyle, correct.
如果第 12 行在第 8 行上，会发生什么情况 ?
What would happen if
line 12 was on line 8?
没有标识，对吧 ?
There would be no identifier, right?
我们将在下一张幻灯片中看到这个案例。
We'll see that case in the next slide.
但是第 12 行上有一个标识，因为
But there is an identifier
on line 12 because
通过分配到未声明的变量，函数 otherClass 自动创建该函数。
the function otherClass auto created it
by assigning to a non-declared variable.